mediaplatform.com 2013-12-12

# Privacy | MediaPlatform | Best in Class Webcasting and Enterprise YouTube

**Your privacy is our top concern. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy:**

  * We will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes
  * We will never share your contact information with other users.
  * Any sensitive information that you provide will be secured with all industry standard protocols and technology

Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable data may be used or shared will be posted in updates to our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use the MediaPlatform® service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices policy to learn more about:

  * What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by MediaPlatform®.
  * How the information is used.
  * With whom the information may be shared.
  * How you can access and change your Account information.
  * What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected by MediaPlatform®.
  * How to contact us.
  * If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact MediaPlatform® by email at [**privacy@mediaplatform.com**](mailto:privacy@mediaplatform.com).

MediaPlatform, Inc. (MediaPlatform) is a participant in the Safe Harbor program developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union. MediaPlatform has certified that they adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles agreed upon by the U.S. and the E.U. The Safe Harbor certification for MediaPlatform can be viewed on the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Safe Harbor Web site at this link: [**http://export.gov/safeharbor/**](http://export.gov/safeharbor/ "Safe Harbor program").

* * *

## Information Collection

**Registration**  
In order to become a MediaPlatform® user, you must first create an account. To create an account you are required to provide the following contact information: name, email and choose a password. In some cases, you may be required to enter other personal information.

**Information about your Contacts**  
In order to invite others to view your webcasts, you will enter their email addresses (either manually or via import). This information will be used by MediaPlatform to send your invitation including a message that you write. The email addresses of people that you invite will be used only to send your invitation.

All information that you enter or upload about your contacts will be covered by the same terms of this privacy policy as cover your own personally identifiable information.

**Information Use**  
MediaPlatform is webcast creation software that allows the user to easily create rich media presentations with synched, dynamic content. Information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by MediaPlatform from the software (such as, by way of example, number of webcasts created and patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by MediaPlatform. This information can be utilized by MediaPlatform in such manner as MediaPlatform, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate.

**MediaPlatform Communications**  
MediaPlatform will communicate with you through email and notices posted on the MediaPlatform website. These emails from MediaPlatform will be related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices about hosting usage, upgrades, important information and services. MediaPlatform may also send news, information on using our products and other relevant information. You may request not to receive these communications at any time by emailing [**unsubscribe@ mediaplatform.com**](mailto:unsubscribe@mediaplatform.com) with the word “unsubscribe” in the subject.

**Customized Content**  
Information you provide at registration is also used to customize your experience within the software. For example, when you login to your account we For example, when you login to your account we will display current usage information.

* * *

## Information Sharing

**Sharing Information With Third Parties**  
MediaPlatform takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personally identifiable with third parties to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services. For instance, we may use a credit card processing company to bill users for subscription fees. These third parties will not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.

We may provide aggregated data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. We may segment our users by industry, geographic location, company. If you would like to be excluded from the aggregated research or products based upon aggregated data about our users’ activities on the site, please email customer service.

**Partnering with Other Organizations to Offer Combined Services**  
MediaPlatform partners with other online services to give you the combined results of both services. For example we partner with Internet Content Distribution Networks to provide the best hosting and streaming video experience to your viewers. In these cases, your personally identifiable information will only be passed from MediaPlatform to the partner to use the combined service.

**Communications Between Users**  
Many emails you initiate through MediaPlatform, a webcast invitation sent to a non-user for instance, will list your email address and name in the header of the message.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

**Accessing and Changing Your Account Information**  
You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your MediaPlatform account, at any time by accessing the account settings within MediaPlatform. You can also close your account through MediaPlatform. If you close your MediaPlatform account, we may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the MediaPlatform Privacy Policy that you have previously agree to. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the MediaPlatform service, please send your request to [**accounts@mediaplatform.com**](mailto:accounts@mediaplatform.com). Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with MediaPlatform under your name.

**Security**  
In order to secure your personal information, access to your data in MediaPlatform is password-protected, and certain data such as credit card information is NOT stored on MediaPlatform but is instead completely managed by a dedicated credit-card processing vendor. To protect any data you store on our servers we also regularly audit our system for possible vulnerabilities and attacks and we use a tier-one secured-access data center.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
MediaPlatform may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

**Questions or Comments**  
If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please email us at [**privacy@mediaplatform.com**](mailto:privacy@mediaplatform.com) or contact us at:

MediaPlatform  
Attn: Privacy Policy Issues  
8383 Wilshire Blvd  
Suite 750  
Beverly Hills, CA 90211
